## **ABOUT ME**

Full-stack web developer with 10+ years of experience in the healthcare field. I have always enjoyed analyzing issues presented by clients and using my knowledge to develop a plan which supports their goals. A career in web development would allow me to continue improving people's lives while having a broader impact. My attention to detail, critical thinking skills and ability to collaborate with peers allow me to solve problems effectively.

# SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

Languages HTML5, CSS, SASS, JavaScript (ES6), Ruby, SQL Front-End Frameworks React, ¡Query, Ajax, Bootstrap Back-End Frameworks Node.js, Express, EJS, ERB Systems, CMS & Databases Git, PostgreSQL, npm, asdf, jekyll Testing Cypress, Mocha/Chai, Storybook, Jest, rspec, circleCl

## **PROJECTS**

ListKeeper - An emergency contact app disguised as a TODO list. Built with Next.js, Twilio, Sendgrid, MongoDB and Vercel.

Easy Ride - A purpose built website for the Victoria Theraputic Riding Association, to allow them to schedule rides, manage payments and track progress reports. Built with React, Material UI, Rails and PostgreSQL.

Resource Wall - A SPA to save URLs & categorize them into various different topic boards. Made with jQuery, jQuery-UI, Bootstrap, SASS, Navigo, Express, PostgreSQL

Scheduler - A CRUD application for interview appointments. Build with SASS, React, express, SQL, jest, Storybook and Cypress.

Tweeter - A twitter clone single page application using CSS, HTML, JavaScript, and ¡Query.

### **EXPERIENCES**

Registered Massage Therapist

- November 2017-August 2020: Cardinal Point Health Centre
- January 2013-November 2017: Cedar Hill Sport Therapy Clinic
- August 2010-March 2013: WestShore Wellness and Chiropractic
- June 2010-August 2020: Locum (short-term sick or vacation leave)

As a sole proprietor, I managed all aspects of treating the clients in collaboration with other practitioners. Starting with the intake process where I consulted with the client to understand their needs. Along with the treatments I would also be responsible for processing insurance claims and documenting the medical history in a secure and confidential manner.



# **Nicole** Woodcock

Web Developer

woodcock.np@gmail.com

**1** 250 893 9293

in npwoodcock

npwxx

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Diploma of Web Development**

Lighthouse Labs August 2020 - November 2020

#### **Diploma in Massage Therapy**

West Coast College Of Massage Therapy Jan 2008 - May 2010

#### **LANGUAGES**

**English (Native)** 

French (Beginner)

#### **INTERESTS**

Hiking

Geocaching

**Board Games & Puzzles**